import React from 'react';

const animalQuestions = [
    {
      question:
        'How many legs does a spider have?',
      answers: ['Six', 'Eight', 'Four', 'Two'],
      correct: 'vinayak',
      questionId: 1
    },
    {
        question:
          'What’s the name of a place you go to see lots of animals?',
        answers: ['Park', 'School', 'Bus', 'Zoo'],
        correct: 'zoo',
        questionId: 2
      },
      {
        question:
          'What type of fish is Nemo?',
        answers: ['Goldfish', 'Clownfish', 'Blobfish', 'Bluefish'],
        correct: 'Clownfish',
        questionId: 3
      },
      {
        question:
          'What do caterpillars turn into?',
        answers: ['Tigers', 'Monsters', 'Butterflies', 'Zebras'],
        correct: 'Butterflies',
        questionId: 4
      },
      {
        question:
          'How many pairs of wings do bees have?',
        answers: ['Eleven', 'Four', 'Two', 'One'],
        correct: 'Two',
        questionId: 5
      },
      {
        question:
          'What is a doe?',
        answers: ['What pizza is made of', 'Female deer', 'Space behind a frogs knees', 'Bear toes'],
        correct: 'Female deer',
        questionId: 6
      },
      {
        question:
          'What is a group of lions called?',
        answers: ['a pack', 'a liars', 'a beast', 'a pride'],
        correct: 'a pride',
        questionId: 7
      },
      {
        question:
          'What’s the first thing a caterpillar usually eats after it’s born?',
        answers: ['a pack', 'a liars', 'a beast', 'a pride'],
        correct: 'a pride',
        questionId: 8
      },
      {
        question:
          'The trumpeter swan—North America’s largest waterfowl—weighs about how many pounds?',
        answers: ['30', '10', '50', '70'],
        correct: '30',
        questionId: 9
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which of the following animals is not nocturnal?',
        answers: ['Skunk', 'Leopard', 'Tiger', 'Sheep'],
        correct: 'Sheep',
        questionId: 10
      },
      {
        question:
          'Walruses can eat about how many clams in one day?',
        answers: ['5,000', '10,000', '12,000', '16,000'],
        correct: '5,000',
        questionId: 11
      },
      {
        question:
          'What is a baby rabbit called?',
        answers: ['Doe', 'Buck', 'Kit','Hare'],
        correct: 'Kit',
        questionId: 12
      },
      {
        question:
          'How many koalas stacked on top of one another does it take to reach the height of a male giraffe—the world’s tallest land animal?',
        answers: ['7','2', '4', '50'],
        correct: '7',
        questionId: 13
      },
      {
        question:
          'An ant says, “Danger ahead!” by doing what?',
        answers: ['squealing', 'running toward water', 'rolling on its back', ' oozing chemicals'],
        correct: ' oozing chemicals',
        questionId: 14
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which of the following is not a type of penguin?',
        answers: ['waterland','emperor', 'chinstrap', 'macaroni'],
        correct: 'waterland',
        questionId: 15
      },
    ]

const spaceQuestions = [
        {
          question:
            'What is the bright glow around the “head” of a comet called?',
          answers: ['Ring', 'Coma', 'Halo', 'Crown'],
          correct: 'Coma',
          questionId: 1
        },
        {
            question:
              'Which of the following did people used to think seeing a comet signified?',
            answers: ['Disaster', 'Disease', 'Death', 'All the above'],
            correct: 'All the above',
            questionId: 2
          },
          {
            question:
              'What is the name of the famous comet that can be seen from Earth about every 75 years?',
            answers: ['Hale-Bopp', 'Shoemaker-Levy 9', 'Halley’s Comet', 'Pluto'],
            correct: 'Halley’s Comet',
            questionId: 3
          },
          {
            question:
              'How many tails does a comet have?',
            answers: ['Most have 2', 'Only 1', 'Roughly 3', 'At least 5' ],
            correct: 'Most have 2',
            questionId: 4
          },
          {
            question:
              'What is the name of a well known meteor shower that peaks in August each year?',
            answers: ['Persieds','Pleiades', 'Summer Shower', 'Orion'],
            correct: 'Perseids',
            questionId: 5
          },
          {
            question:
              'What is the scientific name for a shooting star?',
            answers: ['Comet', 'Asteroid', 'Falling star', 'Meteor'],
            correct: 'Meteor',
            questionId: 6
          },
          {
            question:
              'What is the name of a well known meteor shower that peaks each November?',
            answers: ['Leonids', 'Linus', 'Northern Lights', 'Winter Shower'],
            correct: 'Leonids',
            questionId: 7
          },
        ]
const socialStudiesQuestions = [
    {
        question:
            'Which ocean is off the California coast?',
        answers: ['Atlantic', 'Indian', 'Pacific', 'Red sea'],
        correct: 'Pacific',
        questionId: 1
    },
    {
        question:
            'What is something you hit with a hammer?',
        answers: ['Screw', 'Rubberband', 'Nail', 'Wrench'],
        correct: 'Nail',
        questionId: 2
    },
    {
        question:
            'What colors are the stars on the American flag?',
        answers: ['Red', 'Orange', 'Blue', 'White'],
        correct: 'White',
        questionId: 3
    },
    {
        question:
            'What fruit do kids traditionally give to teachers?',
        answers: ['Pizza', 'Orange', 'Apple', 'iPod'],
        correct: 'Apple',
        questionId: 4
    },
    {
        question:
            'What do you use to write on a blackboard?',
        answers: ['Grapes', 'Sharpie', 'Crayon', 'Chalk'],
        correct: 'Chalk',
        questionId: 5
    },
    {
        question:
            'Which ocean is off the California coast?',
        answers: ['Atlantic', 'Indian', 'Pacific', 'Red sea'],
        correct: 'Pacific',
        questionId: 0
    },
    {
        question:
            'What is something you hit with a hammer?',
        answers: ['Screw', 'Rubberband', 'Nail', 'Wrench'],
        correct: 'Nail',
        questionId: 0
    },




function Quiz(props) {
    return (
        <div>
            
        </div>
    );
}

export default Quiz;